<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wellness</string>
    <string name="day_1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="day_2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="day_3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="day_4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="day_5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="day_6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="day_7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="day_8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="day_9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="day_10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="day_11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="day_12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="day_13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="day_14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="day_15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="day_16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="day_17">Day 17</string>
    <string name="day_18">Day 18</string>
    <string name="day_19">Day 19</string>
    <string name="day_20">Day 20</string>
    <string name="day_21">Day 21</string>
    <string name="day_22">Day 22</string>
    <string name="day_23">Day 23</string>
    <string name="day_24">Day 24</string>
    <string name="day_25">Day 25</string>
    <string name="day_26">Day 26</string>
    <string name="day_27">Day 27</string>
    <string name="day_28">Day 28</string>
    <string name="day_29">Day 29</string>
    <string name="day_30">Day 30</string>
    <string name="title_1">Morning Rituals</string>
    <string name="title_2">Start Your Day with a Glass of Water</string>
    <string name="title_3">Practice Morning Meditation</string>
    <string name="title_4">Write Down Daily Intentions</string>
    <string name="title_5">Mindful Eating</string>
    <string name="title_6">Eat Mindfully</string>
    <string name="title_7">Start the Day with a Balanced Breakfast</string>
    <string name="title_8">Limit Sugar Intake</string>
    <string name="title_9">Hydration Habits</string>
    <string name="title_10">Carry a Water Bottle</string>
    <string name="title_11">Swap Sugary Drinks for Water</string>
    <string name="title_12">Drink Water Before Each Meal</string>
    <string name="title_13">Physical Activity</string>
    <string name="title_14">Move for 30 Minutes a Day</string>
    <string name="title_15">Take the Stairs</string>
    <string name="title_16">Stretch Regularly</string>
    <string name="title_17">Sleep Hygiene</string>
    <string name="title_18">Set a Consistent Bedtime</string>
    <string name="title_19">Limit Screen Time Before Bed</string>
    <string name="title_20">Create a Relaxing Bedtime Routine</string>
    <string name="title_21">Mental Wellness</string>
    <string name="title_22">Practice Gratitude Daily</string>
    <string name="title_23">Journal Your Thoughts</string>
    <string name="title_24">Limit Social Media Use</string>
    <string name="title_25">Self-Care</string>
    <string name="title_26">Schedule “Me” Time</string>
    <string name="title_27">Pamper Yourself Once a Week</string>
    <string name="title_28">Set Healthy Boundaries</string>
    <string name="title_29">Mindfulness Practices</string>
    <string name="title_30">Practice Deep Breathing</string>
    <string name="text_1">Begin each day by drinking a glass of water to hydrate your body, boost metabolism, and kickstart your energy.</string>
    <string name="text_2">Take 5~10 minutes each morning to meditate. This helps set a calm tone for the day and improves mental clarity.</string>
    <string name="text_3">Reflect on what you want to accomplish today and set positive intentions. This simple act can add purpose and focus to your day.</string>
    <string name="text_4">Focus on each bite, chew slowly, and savor the flavors. Mindful eating enhances digestion and prevents overeating.</string>
    <string name="text_5">Choose a nutritious breakfast with protein, fiber, and healthy fats to fuel your body and keep your energy steady.</string>
    <string name="text_6">Reducing added sugar helps stabilize energy levels, reduces mood swings, and benefits overall health.</string>
    <string name="text_7">Keep a water bottle with you throughout the day to remind yourself to drink water regularly.</string>
    <string name="text_8">Replace sodas and sugary drinks with water or herbal tea. This cuts down on empty calories and supports hydration.</string>
    <string name="text_9">Drinking water before meals can help you stay hydrated and may prevent overeating.</string>
    <string name="text_10">Engage in any form of exercise—walking, running, or cycling. Regular movement is key for maintaining physical and mental health.</string>
    <string name="text_11">Opt for stairs over elevators to add some extra movement into your day and build leg strength.</string>
    <string name="text_12">Include stretching sessions throughout the day to improve flexibility and relieve muscle tension.</string>
    <string name="text_13">Going to bed and waking up at the same time each day helps regulate your internal clock and improve sleep quality.</string>
    <string name="text_14">Avoid screens at least an hour before bedtime to improve melatonin production and encourage better sleep.</string>
    <string name="text_15">Develop a calming routine—like reading or taking a warm bath—to help signal your body that it’s time to wind down.</string>
    <string name="text_16">Write down three things you’re grateful for each day. This simple practice can shift your mindset towards positivity.</string>
    <string name="text_17">Take a few minutes each day to journal your thoughts. It’s a great way to release stress and reflect on your feelings.</string>
    <string name="text_18">Set boundaries for social media time to avoid mental burnout and comparison. Try a digital detox day or limit screen time.</string>
    <string name="text_19">Dedicate a specific time each week just for yourself. Whether it’s reading, painting, or relaxing, this time is for you.</string>
    <string name="text_20">Treat yourself to a small indulgence like a face mask, a massage, or a warm bubble bath to recharge.</string>
    <string name="text_21">Practice saying "no" to things that drain you. Setting boundaries is essential for preserving your mental and emotional health.</string>
    <string name="text_22">Try deep breathing exercises for 5 minutes daily to lower stress and bring a sense of calm and focus.</string>
    <string name="text_23">Spend time in nature and notice the sights, sounds, and smells around you. Being in nature can help reduce stress and boost mood.</string>
    <string name="text_24">Take a 5-minute pause to observe your surroundings and check in with yourself. This can help refresh your mind during busy days.</string>
    <string name="text_25">A clutter-free workspace can improve focus, increase productivity, and help reduce stress.</string>
    <string name="text_26">Choose three main tasks to complete each day. Prioritizing helps you stay focused and accomplish more with less overwhelm.</string>
    <string name="text_27">Use a timer to remind yourself to take short breaks. Regular breaks prevent burnout and boost overall productivity.</string>
    <string name="text_28">Spend a few minutes each day connecting with friends or family, even if it’s just a quick message or call.</string>
    <string name="text_29">Engage fully in conversations by listening attentively and without interruption. This strengthens relationships and understanding.</string>
    <string name="text_30">Make it a habit to say “thank you” and acknowledge others. A small gesture of gratitude can uplift both you and the recipient.</string>

</resources>